{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1. In distributed systems the transportation delays are detrimental to stability due to which of the following reasons ?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "They produce transients",
        "b": "They produce attenuation",
        "c": "They produce a phase lag",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "2. Losses in a centrifugal compressor are due to _____",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Inlet losses",
        "b": "Impeller channel losses",
        "c": "Diffuser losses",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "3. Which type of blower is preferred for fluid bed reactor ?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Centrifugal blower",
        "b": "Positive displacement blower",
        "c": "Regenerative blower",
        "d": "Helical screw blower"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "4. The position and velocity errors of a type-2 system are",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Constant, Constant",
        "b": "Constant, Infinity",
        "c": "Zero, Constant",
        "d": "Zero, Zero"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "5. The characteristics of the PI controller is _____ gain at ______ frequency.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Infinite, Zero",
        "b": "Zero, High",
        "c": "Zero, Low",
        "d": "Zero, Infinite"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	{
      "question": "6. The term hysteresis is associated with",
      "answers": {
        "a": "ON-OFF control",
        "b": "P-control",
        "c": "PI-control",
        "d": "PID-control"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },	
	
	
	{
      "question": "7. In a closed loop control system, PI controller is preferred compared to P controller cause,",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Fast response",
        "b": "High gains",
        "c": "Zero steady state error",
        "d": "Low overshoot"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	{
	 "question": "8. The controller ,which is highly sensitive to noice is,",
      "answers": {
        "a": "PI Controller",
        "b": "PD Controller",
        "c": "ON-OFF Controller",
        "d": "Integral control action"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
	 "question": "9. Which of the following is created by blowers?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Air flow",
        "b": "Water flow",
        "c": "Wastewater flow",
        "d": "Any fluid flow"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
	 "question": "10. What is the purpose of the blowers?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Decrease air flow",
        "b": "Increase air flow",
        "c": "Create Vacuum",
        "d": "Increase fluid flow"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
  ]
}
